+91 7737366393

risheetajain309@gmail.com

India, PALI, Gundochiya bas, 306401

Risheeta Jain

EDUCATION

PGDM, MIT Pune, India, Pune

2023 - Now

B.Tech Hons (Computer Science), MIT Indore, India, Indore

2017 - 2021

SKILLS

Flutter Experienced
Firebase Skillful
Node JS Beginner
React JS Beginner
Dart Experienced

LANGUAGES

English Hindi

COURSES

Flutter Trainer, Acte Coaching Chennai

B-Certificate, 2 MP Armd Sqn Ncc Indore

C-Certificate, 2MP Armd Sqn Ncc Indore

Programming in Java (87%), Coaching Chennai Programming in Java, Indian Institute of Technology, Kharagpur, Linkedin: risheeta-jain

Github: risheetajain

https://auth.geeksforgeeks.org/user/flutterwings/articles

Flutter Developer

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With over three years of experience as a skilled Flutter developer, I specialise in creating user interfaces and mobile applications using Flutter and Dart. My expertise includes unique widgets, API integration, effective UI/UX design with animations, and different payment gateways. Additionally, I have experience with NodeJS API creation and managing the team.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer, Somnath Infotech

January 2024 - March 2024

Create and manage Node.js apps with performance and scalability in mind.

Using React.js, create and develop responsive user interfaces to provide smooth user experiences.

Using Flutter, create cross-platform mobile apps that work consistently on both iOS and Android platforms.

Work together with team members and project managers to ensure that deliverables and milestones are met on schedule.

Junior Software Engineer, Drevol Software LLC, India, Vadodara

July 2022 - November 2023

Build cross-platform mobile apps using Flutter, emphasising user experience and performance.

Work together with team members and project managers to ensure that deliverables and milestones are met on schedule.

Flutter Developer, TechMET Solutions, India, Nashik

July 2021 - July 2022

Create and develop complex Flutter applications.

PERSONAL INFO

Date of birth **30 September 2000**

Nationality **Indian**

HOBBIES

Traveling

Learning New Skills

Create unique Flutter packages by utilising the features of the native platform.

Convert designs into responsive, high-caliber UI code.

Developer Track Intern, Magical Solutions, India, Indore

January 2021 - June 2021

Under supervision, support the creation and testing of Flutter apps.

Work together as a team to translate UI/UX designs into usable code.

Gain practical experience and learn how to implement best practices for Flutter development.

Flutter Developer Intern, Fintech IT Solutions LLP, India, Jodhpur

May 2020 - December 2020

Assist in developing and testing Flutter applications under supervision.

Contribute to documentation efforts and knowledge sharing within the team.

PROJECTS

Savdhan Bharat

January 2024 - February 2024

Appstore:- https://apps.apple.com/in/app/savd-han-bharat/id6475668649

Playstore:- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=app.savdhan_bharat.com

TechMET Admin Panel and Website

March 2022 - April 2022

Key Points: Flutter Animations, Firebase Cloud Firestore, Animations, Responsiveness, and loading images and the website faster

http://techmetsolutions.com/#/

Node JS Stripe Webhook for payment

January 2023 - January 2023

Techstack: Node JS, Stripe, Azure hosting

It is Webhook for Stripe for handling different events and updating POS things.

Honest Stripe Checkout Website / Windows Dashboard

October 2022 - September 2023

Integrated Stripe API and Added Cloud firestore database and hosted on firebase hosting

United We Stand Nashik

April 2022 - May 2022

Key Points: Paytm Payment Gateway with custom text fields buttons

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tech-metsolutions.united_we_stand_nashik

TO THE MOON

June 2022 - July 2022

Key Points: WebSockets, Rive animation, and Paytm payment gateway

Cricstock

February 2022 - April 2022

Key Points: Cashfree payment gateway, Push notifications with a different sounds on different kinds of notification

Lovin Choco

August 2021 - September 2021

Key Points: Firebase, Razorpay Payment Gateway

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tech-metsolutions.cake_shop

Lovin

October 2021 - December 2021

Key Points: Custom bottom navigation bar and Tinder-swapping.

Link:- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.techmetsolutions.lovin

Steel Mandi (January 2022-May 2023)

February 2022 - May 2023

Upgrade the flutter version and make responsiveness for the Web, Google Maps, Websockets